<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Unity 3d &#8211; Synnestra</title>
	<atom:link href="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//portfolio-cat/unity-3d/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 13:59:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/07/WhatsApp_Image_2023-08-03_at_10.36.36_PM-removebg-preview-removebg-preview-2-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Unity 3d &#8211; Synnestra</title>
	<link>https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>XANA Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//portfolio/xana-metaverse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//?post_type=portfolio#038;p=986</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to the boundless universe of XANA Metaverse, an innovative and immersive mobile-based game that redefines the concept of virtual worlds. Embrace the possibilities of next-generation technology as you dive into a multiplayer environment where endless adventures and interactions await you within the virtual worlds we proudly call &#8220;virtual words.&#8221; With XANA, the power of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to the boundless universe of XANA Metaverse, an innovative and immersive mobile-based game that redefines the concept of virtual worlds. Embrace the possibilities of next-generation technology as you dive into a multiplayer environment where endless adventures and interactions await you within the virtual worlds we proudly call &#8220;virtual words.&#8221;</p>



<p>With XANA, the power of creation is in your hands. Craft your own unique worlds, tailored to your imagination, and share them effortlessly with fellow players. Whether you envision a tranquil paradise, a bustling cityscape, or an otherworldly realm, XANA&#8217;s user-friendly interface allows you to bring your creations to life with minimum effort, making you a true architect of the Metaverse.</p>



<p>Explore the captivating landscapes of other players&#8217; creations as you visit their worlds. Wander through breathtaking landscapes, unlock mysteries, and embark on thrilling quests in these shared virtual spaces. XANA fosters a vibrant and interconnected community, where players can connect, cooperate, and socialize in ways never before possible.</p>



<p>Furthermore, XANA Metaverse integrates the groundbreaking concept of Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) into its virtual ecosystem. Proudly display your unique and rare NFT collections directly within your created worlds. Showcase your prized possessions, from valuable art pieces to legendary equipment, and let other players admire your treasures as they traverse through your imaginative realms.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" width="1024" height="1024" src="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-6-1024x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1110" srcset="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-6-1024x1024.png 1024w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-6-300x300.png 300w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-6-150x150.png 150w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-6-768x768.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Trading becomes a captivating experience in XANA. Engage in secure and exciting exchanges with other players, leveraging your NFTs to barter, negotiate, and form meaningful connections within the Metaverse. Build a reputation as a skilled trader or a generous benefactor, shaping the dynamics of the virtual economy in this ever-evolving world.</p>



<p>Unleash your creativity, explore uncharted territories, and connect with a vibrant community in XANA Metaverse. Immerse yourself in a boundless playground of possibilities where your wildest dreams are brought to life, and every adventure is a shared experience in the realm of &#8220;virtual words.&#8221; Are you ready to be a part of the next generation of the Metaverse? Join XANA today and embark on an extraordinary journey like no other.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="2048" height="924" src="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-1-2048x924-3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1113" srcset="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-1-2048x924-3.png 2048w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-1-2048x924-3-1536x693.png 1536w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-1-2048x924-3-600x271.png 600w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-1-2048x924-3-768x347.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 2048px) 100vw, 2048px" /></figure>



<p>In XANA, you wield the power of creation, crafting worlds that spring from your wildest imaginings. Whether you wish to design a serene oasis, a futuristic metropolis, or a mystical realm of magic, our user-friendly interface empowers you to manifest your visions effortlessly, making you the true architect of this vast Metaverse.</p>



<p>Beyond creating your own realms, XANA beckons you to explore the captivating landscapes of fellow players&#8217; creations. Wander through breathtaking terrains, unlock enigmatic mysteries, and embark on thrilling quests as you traverse these shared virtual spaces. The heart of XANA lies in its vibrant and interconnected community, where players connect, cooperate, and socialize in ways that transcend the boundaries of reality.</p>



<p>Delving further into the innovative features of XANA, we have integrated the groundbreaking concept of Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) into our virtual ecosystem. Your NFT collections, ranging from unique art pieces to legendary equipment, become treasured possessions that you can proudly display within your created worlds. Allow other players to admire your prized NFTs and forge meaningful connections as they journey through your imaginative realms.</p>



<p>Trading within XANA becomes a captivating and secure experience. Engage in thrilling exchanges with fellow players, utilizing your NFTs to barter, negotiate, and contribute to the dynamic virtual economy. Whether you aspire to be a skilled trader or a benevolent benefactor, your actions and choices shape the ever-evolving world of XANA.</p>



<p>Unleash your boundless creativity, explore uncharted territories, and become an integral part of a vibrant and diverse community within XANA Metaverse. Immerse yourself in a playground of infinite possibilities, where every adventure is a shared experience, and the collective imagination of players paints the canvas of &#8220;virtual words.&#8221; Step into the next generation of the Metaverse and join XANA today to embark on an extraordinary journey that defies the limits of reality. Together, we will shape a world where dreams flourish and the realms of the virtual and the actual coalesce in wondrous harmony.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SlamDeck</title>
		<link>https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//portfolio/slamdeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//?post_type=portfolio#038;p=979</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Introducing SlamDeck©, a groundbreaking augmented reality experience that elevates the world of printed cards to new heights. Immerse yourself in the realm of French basketball teams and professional clubs, featuring exclusive and collectible cards of their kind. Get up close and personal with your favorite players, including Evan FOURNIER, Rudy GOBERT, Nicolas BATUM, Nando de [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Introducing SlamDeck©, a groundbreaking augmented reality experience that elevates the world of printed cards to new heights. Immerse yourself in the realm of French basketball teams and professional clubs, featuring exclusive and collectible cards of their kind.</p>



<p>Get up close and personal with your favorite players, including Evan FOURNIER, Rudy GOBERT, Nicolas BATUM, Nando de COLO, Marine JOHANNES, Sandrine GRUDA, and Lahaou KONATE. Dive into the world of Nanterre92, Youssoupha FALL, SIG Strabsourg, Sékou DOUMBOUYA, Limoges CSP, Pape SY, Cholet Basket, John COX, SLUC Nancy, Alain KOFFI, and BCM Gravelines-Dunkerque, with a roster of over 110 players already available!</p>



<p>Exciting Features: </p>



<p>• Unleash the power of augmented reality by flashing a card to reveal unique and useful information about each player. Click on icons to delve into their world. </p>



<p>• Browse the comprehensive index, access statistical data, and immerse yourself in captivating player bios and collection insights.</p>



<p> • Stay connected with your favorite players through seamless integration with social networks, facilitating direct interaction.</p>



<p> • Measure up against the towering Youssoupha FALL, standing at an impressive 2m20, and snap a memorable picture alongside him. </p>



<p>• Engage in thrilling gameplay with your printed SlamDeck cards, drawing random statistics and exploring rules points. </p>



<p>• Take charge as the coach, create your dream team, and challenge your friends with virtual cards available in your smartphone&#8217;s index. </p>



<p>• Unlock unique players and unveil the true essence of French basketball through our innovative collection.</p>



<p></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" src="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1117" style="width:840px;height:472px" width="840" height="472" srcset="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff.png 1920w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-1536x864.png 1536w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-600x338.png 600w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Coverfff-768x432.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></figure>



<p>French Basketball celebrates the love of the game, while SlamDeck introduces innovation and cutting-edge technology to enhance your collecting experience like never before.</p>



<p>Download SlamDeck now and delve into a world of exhilarating basketball card collections, immersive gameplay, and captivating augmented reality. Embark on a thrilling journey as you collect, play, and savor the joy of French basketball in a whole new dimension!</p>



<p></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dinosaur Space Program</title>
		<link>https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//portfolio/dinosaur-space-program/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//?post_type=portfolio#038;p=974</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; is an exhilarating and cleverly designed light-strategy card game that seamlessly fuses prehistoric creatures with space exploration, all while sprinkling in a dash of mischief. In this captivating game, players assume the roles of ambitious dinosaurs, each vying to construct rockets and cunningly sabotage their fellow competitors. The ultimate goal is to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; is an exhilarating and cleverly designed light-strategy card game that seamlessly fuses prehistoric creatures with space exploration, all while sprinkling in a dash of mischief. In this captivating game, players assume the roles of ambitious dinosaurs, each vying to construct rockets and cunningly sabotage their fellow competitors. The ultimate goal is to either be the first to successfully build a rocket or outwit adversaries and be the last player standing to claim glorious victory.</p>



<p>The game&#8217;s rules are elegantly straightforward, ensuring ease of learning and swift gameplay. To embark on this cosmic adventure, players are required to download a free companion app, which serves as an integral part of the gaming experience. As the game commences, each player must tactically take a single action on their turn: either play a card from their hand to advance their rocket&#8217;s construction or draw a new card to enhance their strategic options. The device containing the app is then passed to the next player in line, keeping the pace of action brisk and engaging.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Capture2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1123" style="width:826px;height:465px" width="826" height="465"/></figure>



<p>However, there is a thrilling twist within the game—a looming and menacing meteor threat. As the game unfolds, a meteor strike can unexpectedly descend upon Earth during a player&#8217;s turn. The unfortunate player faced with this cosmic catastrophe is immediately eliminated from the game. This tantalizing element of suspense and urgency heightens the excitement, prompting players to devise strategic maneuvers, all while vigilantly anticipating potential meteor strikes.</p>



<p>&#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; is more than just a card game; it is a compelling and interactive experience that promises hours of entertainment. Its carefully crafted blend of strategic decision-making, playful interactions, and a hint of luck keeps players fully engaged and eager to revisit the prehistoric space adventure. So gather your loved ones, friends, or fellow dino-enthusiasts, and embark on this whimsical yet tactical journey, complete with rockets, dinosaurs, and cosmic chaos. As you immerse yourselves in this thrilling card game, brace for epic rocket launches, laughter-filled sabotage, and cosmic surprises that await in &#8220;Dinosaur Space Program.&#8221;</p>



<p></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Capture.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1122" style="width:827px;height:466px" width="827" height="466"/></figure>



<p>&#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; is an imaginative and meticulously designed light-strategy card game that transports players into a captivating world where prehistoric creatures venture into the vastness of space. With the fusion of dinosaurs and cosmic exploration, the game offers a delightful blend of adventure and mischievous antics that promise an unforgettable gaming experience.</p>



<p>In this engrossing game, each player assumes the role of an ambitious dinosaur, competing with fellow players to build rockets that will propel them into space. The objective is twofold: be the first to successfully construct a rocket and launch it into the cosmos or, cunningly outmaneuver rivals and be the last dinosaur standing in the cosmic race to claim ultimate victory.</p>



<p>&#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; prides itself on its straightforward and accessible gameplay, making it enjoyable for players of all ages. To participate, players need to download the free companion app, which serves as a valuable tool throughout the game. As the adventure commences, each player&#8217;s turn consists of making a strategic decision—either playing a card from their hand to advance their rocket&#8217;s construction or drawing a new card to expand their array of tactics. The inclusion of the companion app ensures a smooth and seamless gaming experience, as players pass the device to the next participant, keeping the action lively and engaging.</p>



<p>However, amidst the thrilling rocket-building pursuits, a sense of cosmic unpredictability prevails with the meteor threat. During the game, meteors may ominously descend upon Earth, with the unfortunate consequence of eliminating the player facing this cosmic calamity from the game. This compelling twist instills an element of suspense and urgency, as players must strategize meticulously while keenly keeping an eye out for potential meteor strikes.</p>



<p>&#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; elevates the traditional card game with its captivating narrative and interactive gameplay. It transcends conventional boundaries, creating an immersive experience that sparks the imagination and fosters meaningful connections among players. Whether competing against friends, family, or fellow gaming enthusiasts, players will find themselves engrossed in thrilling rocket launches, laughter-filled sabotage, and cosmic surprises that make &#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; a treasured addition to any gaming repertoire.</p>



<p>Gather your favorite group of adventurers and embark on an enthralling journey filled with daring dinosaurs, celestial exploration, and cosmic chaos. &#8220;Dinosaur Space Program&#8221; offers the perfect blend of light strategy, playful interactions, and exciting twists, ensuring that every gaming session is an extraordinary cosmic adventure. Prepare to launch your rockets and embark on a remarkable card game quest that will have players of all ages clamoring for more in this whimsical and strategic space odyssey.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CHIPS Play-to-Earn</title>
		<link>https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//portfolio/chips-play-to-earn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//?post_type=portfolio#038;p=942</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Embark on an extraordinary journey with CHIPS, a groundbreaking play-to-earn mobile metaverse game, leveraging the innovative Cardano blockchain. Our vision goes beyond traditional gaming, as we redefine the gaming experience by not only rewarding players for their engagement but also for embodying moral conduct. CHIPS empowers players to become active participants in a thriving economy, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Embark on an extraordinary journey with CHIPS, a groundbreaking play-to-earn mobile metaverse game, leveraging the innovative Cardano blockchain. Our vision goes beyond traditional gaming, as we redefine the gaming experience by not only rewarding players for their engagement but also for embodying moral conduct.</p>



<p>CHIPS empowers players to become active participants in a thriving economy, centered around two essential tokens: the $CHIP coin and the $CRUMB token. As players immerse themselves in captivating gameplay and complete tasks, they are rewarded with $CRUMB tokens, acting as the gateway to engaging in transactions within the dynamic Chips Metaverse.</p>



<p>Explore the boundless possibilities within our metaverse and:</p>



<ul>
<li>Personalize your Chips avatar, reflecting your individuality and style.</li>



<li>Embark on thrilling adventures through our expansive universe, reaping $CRUMB token rewards along the way.</li>



<li>Engage in exhilarating mini-games that provide both entertainment and rewards.</li>



<li>Showcase positivity and good conduct to earn additional $CRUMB rewards.</li>



<li>Acquire $CHIP coins and passively earn $CRUMB tokens, elevating your gaming experience.</li>
</ul>



<p>At CHIPS, we believe in making gaming meaningful and rewarding. Our rapidly growing community thrives on the value of players&#8217; actions and choices, where their journey towards personal success is intricately woven into a revolutionary play-to-earn experience.</p>



<p>Discover the future of gaming with CHIPS Play-to-Earn on the Cardano blockchain, and unleash your full potential in an ever-evolving metaverse. Join us and experience gaming like never before.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="2532" height="1170" src="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1126" srcset="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed.jpg 2532w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-1536x710.jpg 1536w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-2048x946.jpg 2048w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-600x277.jpg 600w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-768x355.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 2532px) 100vw, 2532px" /></figure>



<p>Welcome to the immersive world of &#8220;CHIPS,&#8221; an innovative play-to-earn mobile metaverse game built on the cutting-edge Cardano blockchain. Get ready to experience gaming like never before as we redefine the way players engage with virtual worlds.</p>



<p>In &#8220;CHIPS,&#8221; players embark on an extraordinary journey where creativity, skill, and moral conduct are celebrated. As you explore the vast universe, complete exciting quests, and conquer challenges, you&#8217;ll be rewarded not only with virtual achievements but also with valuable $CRUMB tokens. These tokens are an integral part of the Chips Metaverse economy, enabling you to engage in a wide range of transactions and interactions within the game.</p>



<p>The game offers an expansive array of features, from personalizing your Chips avatar to reflect your unique style to engaging in exhilarating mini-games that keep you entertained and rewarded. Moreover, we place a strong emphasis on promoting positivity and good conduct. By embodying these virtues in your gameplay, you&#8217;ll earn additional $CRUMB rewards, encouraging a supportive and friendly community.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1559" height="877" src="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-8.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1127" srcset="https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-8.png 1559w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-8-1536x864.png 1536w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-8-600x338.png 600w, https://SynnestraEnterprise.github.io/SynnestraEnterprise//wp-content/uploads/2023/08/unnamed-8-768x432.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1559px) 100vw, 1559px" /></figure>



<p></p>



<p>In the world of &#8220;CHIPS,&#8221; the $CHIP coin plays a pivotal role. Acquiring $CHIP coins not only enhances your in-game experience but also enables you to passively earn $CRUMB tokens, thereby amplifying your journey in the metaverse.</p>



<p>At its core, &#8220;CHIPS&#8221; aims to make gaming meaningful and rewarding, empowering players to become active participants in a thriving virtual economy. Join our growing community, where your actions and choices hold value, and embark on an unforgettable adventure in a play-to-earn experience like no other.</p>



<p>Discover the future of gaming with &#8220;CHIPS&#8221; on the Cardano blockchain and unleash your full potential in an ever-evolving metaverse. Embrace a world where creativity, skill, and virtue are cherished, and the pursuit of personal success is intricately intertwined with a revolutionary play-to-earn experience. Are you ready to take the leap into the extraordinary world of &#8220;CHIPS&#8221;?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
